练习 2-12：寻找连读和滑音。在下面这段话中，尽可能连接
Exercise 2-12 Finding Liaisons and Glides In the following paragraph, connect as
更多词。像前两个句子中那样标出连读，
many of the words as possible. Mark your liaisons as we've done in the first two
并在词与词之间加入 Y 和 W 滑音。练习朗读这段话，
sentences. Add the Y and W glides between the words. Practice reading the paragraph
读三遍，重点放在把词连起来。重新打开 CD，
three times, focusing on running your words together. Turn the CD back on and
我读的时候跟我重复。我会夸张地连接这些词。
repeat after me as I read. I'm going to exaggerate the linking of the words,
drawing it out much longer than would be natural. Hello, my name is Anne. I'm taking
American accent training. There's a lot to learn, but But I hope to make it as
enjoyable as possible.
I should pick up on the American intonation pattern pretty easily, although
the only way to get it is to practice all of the time. I use the up and down or
peaks and valleys intonation more than I used to. I've been paying attention to
pitch, too. It's like walking down a staircase.
I've been talking to a lot of Americans lately and
they tell me that I'm easier to understand. Anyway, I could go on and on,
but the important thing is to listen well and sound good. Well, what do you think?
Do I?